and you have to say out of 86,000
seconds stage was the final stage where
they
[Music]
actually to see any
success engineering atly
[Music]
media came out of both of those
things what's going on folks how are you
guys doing my name is Ryan Perez and
this is hustle Zone TV formerly known as
go live and prosper I'm calling myself
now digital stem cell and and what that
means is that I am a back of all trades
in all things digital and other hyper
focuses and I'm that way because I'm
neurod Divergent I have autism I have
dyslexia and I have uh ADHD so it kind
of gives me uh unique perspectives on
things and I built this website and I
wanted to put like a one minute pitch of
you know what is digital stem cell uh
because a lot of people kind of confused
with what I do because you know some
people know me as a you know a producer
some people know know me as a web
developer some people know me as a lot
of different things I was doing this
video yesterday and you know I was
hoping not to see a soul I see this
brother and you know I seen him walking
okay and I'm like you know he he looks
kind of familiar and I was like you know
maybe I know the guy and I'm like no I
don't know the guy he asked me to fil me
as I was doing my video and that was
pretty kind of him and um uh and then we
just start talking and you know he has a
very interesting story and I you know
and I and I I was like you know
compelled to want to get him on uh onto
the podcast because he has the Hustler
mindset so he is a you know he's a
content creator he's a father he's a
consultant he's a retired vet uh and
shout out to him for that um he is a
Fashion Stylist he is a fashion designer
um I'm probably gonna be one of his
clients because you know he's got some
funky uh bow ties uh over there and and
so I wanted to introduce you all to
Jerry Jones Thank you for having me on
your uh on your channel definitely um
yeah man I was just I was just being
kind I I I told you I saw your hat and I
was like hey I have that
hat you
know I didn't and and and then you
called me out because uh like I I buy
everything from H&M almost everything
from H&M just because of price point and
because it's just my I don't know it's
it's my style for the
until I can
hire that we hey look we blo what we
planted man so we got to take what we
can get I actually been shopping at H&M
for like over 20 years wow yeah that's
crazy and um but yeah you called me out
for the the H&M hat and um but that's
how I know that you you about your your
fashion and and and stuff like that
you're like really good at what you do
so um I'm GNA start off how I normally
start my podcast off um I just want to
hear what is your story so go all the
way back you know as far as you want um
you know the the the floor is yours well
one night in September um my mom and dad
was in a vent
I'm Hey listen no my name is Jerry Jones
thank you all for holding space for me
right now now I am actually uh retired
from the military the United States Navy
uh I am a Navy counselor Chief um and
what that entails is human re resources
so pretty much I'm the plug if whatever
you needed on the ship I found a way to
get it for you and the only thing that's
different now is that I'm retired and
I'm still doing the same thing for all
of my Sailors and all of my friends and
all the people that I meet organically
that inspire me I'm interested about so
like what was the thing that prompted
you to get into the military I went into
the military because my cousin went into
the military and honestly my mom told me
that if I'm not doing anything by the
time I'm 19 anything substantial then
she's going to [ __ ] me off to to boot
camp now you can't ship a 19y old or 18
year old off unwillingly so it was just
a kick in the pants to tell me to get my
stuff together what were your
experiences in the military how did it
shape you how did that experience shape
you they had something that I needed
which was a paycheck so I'm not I wasn't
one of those kids that uh joined
for patriotism you know especially being
a black kid like what I lived in nor
look I'm from norol Virginia and I
didn't even pay attention to the
military side of it because I was so
into doing everything else um but then
when I came home from boot camp I
realized that Norfolk Virginia was the
epicenter of the
Navy you know it's the biggest base in
the
world wow North Virginia yeah so when I
came home and I started I started being
more observant you know and um I'm
seeing all of these decals on people's
cars I was like I never noticed that
before you know and so it it just opened
my eyes up to to what type of place that
I lived in which I never even knew
about in in in my uh in my demographic
in Chesapeake Virginia we were in the
suburbs but you know either you go be a
long shoreman you work at the shipyard
or you just do whatever you feel like
doing you know they let a 18yearold kid
drive an aircraft or excuse me steer an
aircraft carrier so you got a little kid
from Chesapeake
Virginia as a bosen's mate which um
which is I like to I like to uh say
because people that don't know the Navy
you know popy poy was like a boson m he
had the cross anchors on his arms and
everything like that like warriors on
the water you have to drive we have to
steer the ships we have to paint the
ships we have to
lead in junior
capacities and lead a lot of people to
either pull the ship in steer the ship
navigate uh tons of things right and so
everybody in the Navy has their own
little thing to do but um that was my
job I was a deck Seaman I started off as
a deck Seaman and then I became um a
bosen's mate third class and then I went
up to second class and I didn't get to
uh I didn't get to make first class
which is uh an E6 advancement
right but I was able to switch over my
job from that to human resources because
I wasn't challenged like mentally I
wasn't
challenged and I was growing up around
22 23 and I was getting bored you know
and so I finally decided to take on the
role as a departmental career counselor
every time that someone comes up with
something I a problem fixer I'm a
Problem
Solver at one point I well I always used
to call myself Batman um because it was
like I was living in a sitcom every time
I turn around bro I'm fixing something
or putting a fire out and it was always
my my job always consisted of being
reactive you know instead of uh instead
of just acting on my regular stuff
because people you can give people the
information but are they going to take
the information are they going to use
utilize it are they going to are they
going to do it the exact way that you
told them to do it when did you know you
had that gift like when did you know
that you were you know you had the Gift
of Gab you know that you could connect
with people like that throughout my life
uh all my aunties and my uncles and
everything like that when we would go
around I would be in the church choir
and when they had a little functions
they tell you oh go and sing for me for
a dollar baby we gonna give you a dollar
but you know how many dollars these
mother [ __ ] owe
me like what what made you that way like
why did people trust you so much in you
know in solving the problems right like
what was it that was it your upbringing
um you know did you experience something
in your life where you know it it it
propelled you into you know these these
sort of roles you know what were what
was your um what's the background behind
that the simple fact for me is even in
high school
I moved in different Social Circles just
like you a digital stem cell I don't lie
to people I tell them how it is if we
need to fight then we will fight but
most of the time I'm G to talk you down
off the ledge
because the stuff that we come up with
is stupid and we as a people need to do
a little bit better we need to slow down
a little bit and actually think about
what's going on instead of always
reacting and I got that from my homeboy
Big Mike AKA mad Chef uh with mad Chef
apparel you know what I'm saying he's
out in San Diego living his best life
right now retired as
well yeah so um we we US Navy people man
it's like we we take the oath and we
come in and some like it some don't but
a lot of us stay because of our families
right you know what I mean so we stay in
that in that space because it's
comfortable and we're taken care of but
what happens when it's time to ring that
Bell though when it's time to retire or
separate you know I'm the guy who or
people like me in the military the Navy
counselors um we get them ready for
transition outside into the real world
and now I'm on the outside and I have a
gang of people that are really really
really showing and proving their worth
and because I a lot of things recently
have been going on in my life where you
know we say we call people our day
ones know and we usually correlate that
with our blood relatives and things of
that nature right
but it's not it's not those people that
that
uh it's not those people
that that are there for you it's those
people that you are potentially going
out there to die with or die for you
know what I mean that's right and so
those people hold more value in a
certain stent because we were out there
by
ourselves away from our families the
people that we are supposed to be close
with
but we're out protecting them as well
as protecting the country or the world
even you know um so I call them my day
twos so if you ever go on my website or
my Instagram um and it's called Alter
Ego apparel and my uh my Instagram is
future Jones with the Z J NE z um and
alter eego
apparel that's Alter Ego at
apparel um and that is also.com if you
want to reach me for Consulting that's
my email address also it's a Gmail
account everything is synonymous Alter
Ego it started off as Alter Ego
right or excuse me it started off as
alter ego but everybody got Alter Ego
right everybody do something with Alter
Ego the reason I pick Alter Ego is
because I feel like I'm an alien also
right but one part of me is this nice
guy this kid this emotional being the
other part of me is this loud
boisterous human being
that goes into any social setting and
commands
attention does that make sense yeah that
makes sense yeah so I'm not saying that
I'm schizophrenic or anything like that
but what I'm saying is everybody has an
alter ego you have to be an alter ego
you have to tap into your Alter Ego when
you go to work that's right and you have
to uh code switch is what they call it
right right you got a code switch right
so we all have that in us so yeah no I
mean Alter Ego is for everybody this
isn't this is actually an empower
brand um I'm empowering people to alter
their
egos to become the greatest of all
time to become the goat we all we all
talk about goats and stuff like that and
and things of that nature but in the
Navy also I'm I'm a Navy Chief which
also is a goat as well that's our
nickname we're the goats we're uh we're
in the goat Locker like that's our
that's our headquarters and the the
chief's mest is the goat Locker right so
it's a it's a little it mixes everything
in but it all
relates it all relates and it just makes
sense so I I ran with it and it was it
was Rocky at first but people didn't
understand what I was saying until I
pronunce or enunciated the tea and goat
you know then they started getting it
that's right that's right and like you
know that's why I was so compelled to
have you on the show because you know
not only you have a story it's just
you know there was an energy that you
had that um was very compelling that I
sense anyways but you know that's the
whole thing about being a Divergent
thinker um you know is because we see
the world differently and like you were
talking about earlier you were saying um
people you you would solve problems and
that's what happens a lot of us solve
problems but some sometimes people don't
respect the way that it's coming across
sometimes people don't respect um the
person or whatever and in this
particular case like it it seems like
through your life you've you've built
some really strong connections um
because of your integrity you say your
father you know how does that all come
into all of this Alter Ego with you
being a father that's another Alter Ego
that's a role that's a you know so tell
me a little bit about that being a
father well well first off uh being a
father is
everything um I've never want it to be
anything else because we have to get
away from these generation curses that
we have in our community like we have to
change man like what I'm seeing right
now on on my Instagram and and social
media and everything like that like
people all my age in their 40s and 30s
like late 30s early 40s and stuff you
know we're out here living our second
life again because guess what we didn't
get to live the life of a child matter
of fact I was telling I was telling a
couple my homeboys just the other day
right I said yo
no actually it was my cousin because
she's a girl so look I was like look
said something about she say something
about playing video games me and be
playing video games and all this other
stuff and everything like that right and
so I was a little elevated at that time
and I said you know why he play video
games
right and she was like why I said I said
well we play video games to to go back
to our childhood about it think about it
though because that like I said I was 12
years years old and I was told that I
was the man of the house when you say
man what does that mean to you in video
games they don't
correlate they don't correlate men don't
play video games right and if they do
the reason being is because if you just
think about it they're going back to
their childhood to what makes them happy
that's right I I learned how to
skateboard with my son in my 30s in my
late 30
s I'm from Virginia I wanted to always
be like for real wear BBC ice cream Bape
bathing ape all of that good stuff right
so when my son was born I was like yo
there's no clothing out here for him at
a decent
price nothing all the stores they were
Bland in they were Bland in their color
selection so I used to get my clothes
from H&M in the gap for him and I used
to buy him uh matter of fact if you ever
go to my Instagram page Gemini King and
I spelled that with a j j m i n i k i n
g if you go down to the first one the
first my very first post is a picture of
my son and some lime green skinny
jeans that I got from the girls
Department because my son was larger
than
life he meant everything to me he was
the brightest shining star in the
[ __ ] world nothing else mattered to
me but him so going back to your
fatherhood question nothing else matters
because my dad wasn't there for me like
that you know I grew up in a single
parent home and I I had other brothers
also and then I had a younger brother
with me as well so to see a man come and
go out of your life it's just like
whatever but
when that man tries to come back in your
life and you're told you're the man of
the house that's a totally different
[ __ ]
story you see what I'm saying so that's
something that our our our parents
generation should have not they should
not have done that to us they should let
kids be kids and so I'm not pushing that
on my son I want him to go and do
everything he wants to do if he wants to
watch
anime or whatever skateboard what I'm
going to give him the tools because I
never got that and I'm just is excited
to do it with him that's right you see
what I'm saying so it means a lot more
to me than just giving him money to go
do it and then we're not doing any I
don't know what he's doing out there
[ __ ] that we both going out what where
we going we're going to the skate park
let's go you know what I'm
saying so it's
um
being a father is everything and a lot
of my friends
share the
same in the thinking that we have to get
away from our generational curses you
and I uh we were part of the generations
where our dads weren't around um you
know I had a dad that was here but he
was um you know like he was he's like my
stepdad but I call him dad he's like a a
dad for me but he wasn't there because
of the transgressions of of my mother so
real the reality was
that um I never wanted to be like that I
didn't want to grow up like that and I'm
sure you didn't want to grow up like
that so the first thing that I did when
I had my son um or when my my ex had my
son because I you I didn't birth my son
but you know hey we all look man look
look look I know what you're talking
about you ain't
got so like you know like the first
thing I did is like I took him to the
you know the fair you know I took him to
you know that's cway Park you know I
took him to uh the mov movies I did a
lot of fun stuff we did a lot of fun
things um and I really made my life
around him like when I decided to be you
know when his his mom and I uh broke
broke up um I said you can't leave this
house until you give me 5050 uh custody
I want to be in his life when she when
she um when she signed the papers and
she left I called my dad my dad was like
what you doing son you know like you
need to be going out there and going out
and having a you know like your you're
you're go out and date and go out and do
this and I'm like no like I'm going to
make the decision to to be a dad now it
has been a a a rocky rad because I
started my business right when you know
she left so you know and it was and it
was cool because I've been you know an
entrepreneur for uh 10 years but the
reality is is that I got to see my son
grow I got to see every moment I got to
see you know the um you know the the
school plays and um you know and I get
to talk to him about now he's talking
about girls and I get to talk to him
about that you know what I'm saying how
old is he how old is he is uh 14 years
old okay my son's 12 so you know like so
I guess what you know like I think for
us I think it's very important um for us
to change that narrative and I wish I
could look around and say oh man this
brother's not in his life this brother's
not in in his life but a lot of fathers
are a lot of my friends and people that
I grew up with that I that you know that
you know maybe were up to no good all of
them are really good Fathers that from
what from what I observe so I think that
we are as a collective changing The
Narrative of you know of fathers not
being active in you know in children's
lives yeah and and you know you still
got those those few the few that they
like to broadcast on social media and
you know the news and things like that
but it's not the case man we out here
especially when when you are surrounded
by those people you like I I've been
I've been doing a lot of lot of uh
Instagram like reading or listening to
those empowerment for some reason my
algorithm is all empowerment because
that's what I'm I'm on you know um but
yeah no I'm I've been in my son's life
he knows who I am there's never any any
hesitation to to think anything
different you know
and uh the only reason that I'm not with
him was because I was in the military
and once we divorced or went separated
or whatever I had to go off and do what
I had to do for for him and my and
myself but I was not GNA sit there and
follow his
mom without a plan especially when I'm
not from where she's moving to that's
stupid so lightning round questions
let's see here so uh talking or texting
talking okay uh favorite day of the
week
[ __ ]
Wednesday okay uh favorite city in the
US favorite city in the
US oh that's n for real you want me to
ask that yeah God dang it favorite city
in the
US damn
Tacoma Tacoma T Washington nice uh
nickname your parents used to call you
boo last song you ever
downloaded
nario
nario NP
nario who is that go go Google them
nario on Instagram okay MP got a song
called not like this
okay I'll I'll check him out uh would
you rather be able to speak every
language in the world or be able to talk
to
animals [ __ ] I already talked to animals
so every
language favorite favorite
holiday my birthday okay how long does
it take for you to get
[Laughter]
ready ah yeah longer than 30 minutes I
tell you that okay
um uh scale from 1 to 10 um how good of
a driver are
you I'm a Tyrese 10
okay uh fill in the blank fill in the
blank Taylor Swift
is Taylor Swift is that's the only blank
yeah the blank yeah
I okay uh what age do you want to retire
I already retire bro okay invisibility
or uh touche invisibility or super
strength
invisibility and is it wrong for a
vegetarian to eat animal
[Music]
[Laughter]
crackers I'mma break the CH yes is wrong
this is
[Laughter]
violation well um Jerry uh this was this
was amazing podcast um bro you have a
lot of things to say I wish we could I
wish we could talk some more you got me
you got
me I wish we could talk more um the uh I
I think that um we have a like we have a
show called The hustles on jam session
and it's like you know kind of like a
round table I'd love to invite you on
that show and and bring some of your
friends and everybody and we could you
know talk about some of these um you
know cultural issues or not issues but
even talking about just business and
talking about other things so you know
be be happy to invite you squ Ryan when
I tell you I got a
squad my squad is
fears nice why we got a bunch of we got
a bunch of
consumer Killers bro we out here we
grinding because you know why because
we've seen death before we're Fearless
we can do anything we want to do because
we have seen death and we had to
maneuver and get through
it so anybody in the military that you
know or you've seen or that have even if
they serve four years two years whatever
please pay them respect and homage
because it's been times where we have
not wanted to to live our own selves
yeah and through the blessings of the
Ghetto Gospel which is of uh Rod wave um
I I thank him
because he saved my
life and we'll we'll we'll end it with
that that but also please check out all
of my social media um up and coming I'm
trying to get down with thank God it's
natural to be an ambassador for them um
because I love their product and what
they stand for and um I just want to
promote and I promote for free if you if
I if I meet you genuinely out in town
right um and we strike up a
conversation I'll ask you for your
information your your Instagram
information and then I'll follow you
three times on all of my Instagram
platforms and I now I have a Tik Tok
also I only got two posts up there but
I'm gonna start pushing some more stuff
out because I'm trying to Market my Drop
Shipping website um a lot of people
aren't doing that they're not telling
their stories and people want to hear
stories so I'm marketing my Drop
Shipping website and I'm not putting up
anything related or Ely related to me
selling something to you I'm actually
letting you see me and then you figure
it out but I just got word from my
people in Pakistan and my cut and sewn
limited edition Ultra ego hoodies are on
their way to me so with that being said
I'm about to start pushing out some
pre-orders of that so please tune in to
uh my Instagram like he has them on the
screen already and the the Drop Shipping
website if you want to just get some of
the uh the basic ones um the one that
I'm wearing is one of one uh it's
actually a management one because I am
management so with it also being Alter
Ego um I have two different logos so you
can go ahead and check that out so I
have one that's pretty much Prada
inspired because that's my favorite
brand and it's classic and elegant and
then I have this one with the uh this
erratic logo that makes you look like uh
it's some type of Rockstar edgy type of
vibe right and these these logos were
made oh there you go there you go look
at that we famous now I got my man's on
here on the
TV we got all this uh this is really
nice and uh maybe alter eot can sponsor
uh calibr dyslexia um but these are
these these are not these are not nice
These are nice you I appreciate that
shouts out to uh my man Alex deod he's
out of Connecticut he did these up I
told him actually I told my my best
friend Aries about these uh shout out to
4X Debo on Instagram as well and uh
doode logo OR doode unstore Logo that's
D actually can you put that one in there
d i o d di o d yeah where in the in in
your on your website or on the chat on
the link okay on the link okay I mean or
the thing that you got going on right
now okay hold on so d i d i o d
e and it should say it should be logo
after that I want to
say but if not if anybody wants uh a
looking for a graphic designer or
someone to elevate because he is a
genius he is a mad
scientist um I think I did that right it
might have been underscore but he'll
yell at me later but it is what it is U
we got you can send me all the links and
then I'll put it in got plenty more time
but I know Bel laon like I'm like I said
I'm gonna give you these uh these
handmade these handmade uh bow Ti from
him these are yours now um you got two
of them I appreciate it you know what
I'm saying and they are when you when
you touch them you going you going to be
like bro you lying I'm like nope cuz
he's a genius as well I'm telling you I
I hang with
Killers I hang with Killers everything
you need we
got that's awesome that's awesome so um
folks I'm just GNA wrap it up here so
make sure to check out uh we also I just
launched this um you know last week or
not last week a couple weeks this is
called sprs too pardon that's tees
Springs also oh yeah that's teesprings
yeah um oh yeah we gonna link up we we
have to we have to work together now so
this is um this is called made for
dyslexic so everything that I put on my
t-shirts are misspelled on purpose so
you could read that it says don't
recommend a book to us to read uh so
it's everything is misspelled uh because
what we're trying to say to everybody is
that no matter what um you can
understand what we're saying you can
understand what we spelling um you know
and you know if you are trying to
correct our spelling you're just being a
jackass so um you know we are this is
called typoglycemia and Ty what
typoglycemia is is uh you know the fact
that anyone even those who are not
dyslexic can read this and it's funny my
dyslexic Community um tends to uh read
this uh better than they can with normal
writing you know so um you know so check
me out with calibrate dyslexia and then
we have like you know pictures with
Einstein because he was a dyslexic like
Einstein one and that sort of things so
you got the all over print on that I
like that that's nice so and then folks
just make sure to check me out at uh you
know uh digital stem cell this is the
website there's a lot going on but you
know uh this is 20 years of you know
working in this business and doing
community work and and whatnot so make
sure to check me out you're looking for
consultation you're looking for branding
you're looking for any of that all
that's here and we're also looking for
sponsors um uh you know we have 200,000
followers collectively over all social
media platforms um so we're looking for
people that want to advertise on our
social medias and that want to support
um our our movement um and so on and so
forth so thank you so much uh Jerry um
for for coming in this was great this is
a great podcast I really appreciate the
brother peace
out and you have to say out of 86,000
seconds stage was the final stage where
they
[Music]
actually to see any
success engineering atly
[Music]
media came out of both of those things